<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ashley D. Greeley</title>
    <link>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ashley D. Greeley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:45:04 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ashleygreeley.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Earth #24Seven</title>
      <link>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/media/earth24seven/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:45:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/media/earth24seven/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Engineer Allison Evans and graduate student scientist Ashley [Greeley] dress in &amp;lsquo;bunny suits&amp;rsquo; for their work to install particle detectors on a CubeSat instrument. The Compact Radiation Belt Explorer (CeREs) will study the bands of energetic particles that surround Earth, known as the Van Allen radiation belts.&amp;rdquo;
Read more about the #24Seven social media campaign for Earth Day 2016, here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Career Scientist Spotlight</title>
      <link>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/media/earlycareer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:36:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/media/earlycareer/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Be stubborn, both in pursuing research and finding the right opportunity. I honestly believe the most important characteristic of a scientist is stubbornly trucking along no matter what (followed closely by the ability to change their mind when confronted with new evidence).&amp;rdquo;
Read the article on NASA&amp;rsquo;s website here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researchers track slowly splitting &#39;dent&#39; in Earth&#39;s magnetic field</title>
      <link>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/media/sciencedaily/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:34:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/media/sciencedaily/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;One study, led by NASA heliophysicist Ashley Greeley as part of her doctoral thesis, used two decades of data from SAMPEX to show that the SAA is slowly but steadily drifting in a northwesterly direction. The results helped confirm models created from geomagnetic measurements and showed how the SAA&amp;rsquo;s location changes as the geomagnetic field evolves.&amp;rdquo;&amp;quot;
Read the article on Science Daily here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Physics Student Builds Space Weather Satellite</title>
      <link>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/media/physstudent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:24:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/media/physstudent/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ashley Greeley is building a satellite. &amp;ldquo;I know,&amp;rdquo; said Greeley. &amp;ldquo;I tell people that and they always say, &amp;rsquo;that sounds cool!&amp;rsquo; — but seriously, it is really cool.&amp;rdquo;
Read the article at catholic.edu here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Herky Jerky Weirdness of Earth&#39;s Magnetic Field</title>
      <link>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/media/herkyjerky/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 20:52:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/media/herkyjerky/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;But sometimes a satellite is just unlucky. Ashley Greeley, a postdoctoral scholar at NASA Goddard Space Flight Center, recalled a CubeSat that died shortly after launch. During start-up checks and the commissioning phase, “we think that an energetic particle hit it in the wrong place at the wrong time, and we never got data, unfortunately,” she said.&amp;rdquo;
Read the article on EOS here! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/blog/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 22:53:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashleygreeley.github.io/blog/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>I am delving into the world of content management. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to make my codes and projects more available to the public, and to anyone who is looking to replicate my results. Let me know if there&amp;rsquo;s anything you&amp;rsquo;re looking for that isn&amp;rsquo;t here, or if you need help deciphering my code. As a warning, just because I am open to sharing my code does not mean that it&amp;rsquo;s elegant.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
